Guide to the Stanford University, Centennial Office, Records
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Stanford University, Centennial Office, records
1891-1991
1979-1991
SC0696
Stanford University. Centennial Office.
38 Linear feet (74 boxes)
Records include correspondence, minutes, proposals, publications, publicity, photographs, research materials on centennial celebrations at other universities, videotapes, and other materials.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
The records were received via administrative transfer in 1989, as well as collected by the Stanford University Archives from various sources, 1989-2011.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Stanford University began its centennial celebrations in 1985, the centennial of the Founding Grant, and continued through 1991, the centennial of the university's opening day. Highlights included the Cornerstone Weekend in 1987 with classes, panels, and addresses by George P. Shultz, Bernardo Sepulveda Amor of Mexico, and Joe Clark of Canada; a visit from Mikhail Gorbachev; and a weekend finale in 1991 featuring roundtables with Stanford faculty and national figures such as George Shultz, Ted Koppel, Bill Clinton, Milton Friedman, Peter Sellars, and Jack Valenti, and a stadium spectacular with performances by Whoopi Goldberg, Bobby McFerrin, Hiroshima, Joan Baez, and others.
Description of the Collection
The records include correspondence, minutes, proposals, publications, publicity, photographs, research materials on centennial celebrations at other universities, videotapes, and other materials.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Centennial Office.; Stanford University--Centennial; Universities and colleges--Anniversaries, etc.
Collection Contents
- Records, Accession ARCH-1991-173
  - Centennial Correspondence 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Correspondence 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Centennial Correspondence 1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Centennial Correspondence 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Preliminary Planning for the Centennial 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Centennial Planning 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Centennial Planning (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
  - Planning for the Stanford Centennial (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Annual Fund 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Quantum Leap Committee 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Centennial Committee 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Committee 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2-6)
  - Centennial Ideas 1983 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Leland and Jane Stanford Chronology (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - The Founding of Stanford 1885 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Bibliography and Theses on Stanford and the Stanford Family (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Letter from Leland Stanford Junior (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Articles 1884-1885 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Newspaper Articles 1886 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - "The Founding of Stanford" by George Crothers (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photos of Cornerstone Ceremony 1887 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Early photos of San Francisco and Stanford (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Historical Feature Story Materials (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Stanford's Opening Day, Oct 1891 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Observed 1891 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Commencement of 1892 and 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 1892 Commencement (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Quarter Century Milestone 1916 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review, Oct 1931 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Stanford Daily-Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Stanford's Golden Jubilee 1941 (Box 3, Folder 3-8)
  - "Kitchen Cabinet" meeting 1942 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Stanford 50th Anniversary, 1945, class of 1895 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Seventy-Five Years after Founding, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - San Jose Mercury-News on Stanford's Diamond Jubilee, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Harvard's 350th Magazine Articles, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Harvard's 350th publications (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Center for Business and Government (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Harvard's 350th, planning (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Harvard's 350th, Celebration papers (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Harvard's 350th, Harvard University Gazette (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - The Museum of Modern Art (New York), "Vienna 1990" (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Magazine: "Harvard at 350" (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Harvard's 350th, miscellaneous newspapers (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - The Kennedy Center Stage bill, Sep 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Harvard's 350th, The Boston Globe (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Magazine: "The Statue of Liberty Centennial" (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Magazine: The Harvard Factor (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Magazine: "The Harvard Crimson" (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Magazine: "The John F. Kennedy School of Government" (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Harvard Alumni Day (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - The Harvard Club of San Francisco (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gorbachev, Signed document (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Gorbachev, Program (in Russian) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Time Magazine: "Harvard 350 and Going Strong" (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Magazine: "Veritas Reconsidered" (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Book: "Three Fifty" (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newsweek Magazine: "Harvard at 350" (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Magazine: "Washington, the Evergreen State Magazine" (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Book: Mardi Gras" (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Book: "Harvard Review" (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Harvard's 350th, Harvard Crimson (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Harvard San Francisco dinner 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Analysis of Harvard's 350th (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - University of Pennsylvania 250th, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - UCLA Magazine, Summer 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Yosemite Centennial, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Georgetown bicentennial, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Rollins College Centennial 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - University of Maryland 175th Anniversary 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Tech Centennial 1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Drake University Centennial 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - University of Texas Centennial 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - University of North Dakota Centennial 1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Johns Hopkins Medicine 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Pomona College Centennial 1988 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - US Olympic Festival, Minneapolis 1990 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Centennial Celebrations at Other Universities (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Press Clippings 1884-1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Early Centennial 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Palo Alto Times Tribune Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto Times Tribune Centennial Issue, Nov 10, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Founders Day, Mar 10, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Day of the Founding, Nov 11, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
  - Centennial Day of the Founding Press Clippings (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Enabling Act of 1885, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Enabling Act Ceremony, Mar 9, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
  - Stanford Court Hotel, Nov 10, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - Stanford Court Hotel Press Kit (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Campaign Planning (Box 7, Folder 9-12)
  - Centennial Campaign Planning Conference Packet Materials (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Campaign Press Conference 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2-4)
  - Centennial Campaign Launch, Feb 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5-7)
  - Centennial Campaign 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Campaign Conclusion 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Centennial Campaign, post campaign 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Campaign News, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Campaign Press Coverage (Box 8, Folder 12-16)
  - Centennial Campaign Press Coverage (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Cornerstone and Celebration Committee Minutes, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Stanford Daily, Cornerstone Weekend, May 14, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Observer and Campus Report, May 1987 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Cornerstone Weekend 1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Cornerstone Data Entry System (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Events (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Miscellany (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cornerstone T Shirt Orders (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cornerstone Registration Deposits (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Labor List (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Registrants by Zip Code (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony slides (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Handbook (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Photos of Joe Clark, George Shultz, Bernardo Sepulveda (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Arrangements for Bernardo Sepulveda and Joe Clark (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Marchers (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Press Kit (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Organization (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Meal Seating Arrangements (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Cornerstone Ceremony Packet and Letter to Managing Editors (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Letter and Mailing Lists for Government people (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Publicity Originals (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - George Shultz, American Secretary of State (Box 11, Folder 4-6)
  - Bernardo Sepulveda, Mexican Secretary of External Relations (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Joe Clark, Canadian External Affairs Secretary (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
  - Cornerstone Special Invitees (Box 11, Folder 12-14)
  - Cornerstone Confirmation Letters (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cornerstone Confirmations - Speakers (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Cornerstone Faculty / Foreign Ministers Meeting (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Cornerstone Exhibits (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Cornerstone Weekend Speeches (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Cornerstone Letters of Thanks (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cornerstone Congratulations and Replies (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Cornerstone Public Service Announcement (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Cornerstone Publications and Articles (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Cornerstone Program Materials (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Cornerstone Registration (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cornerstone Alumni Association Registration (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Cornerstone Registration Problems (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Cornerstone Wine Letters (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Cornerstone TV Packet (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Cornerstone - Shultz, Sepulveda, Clark (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cornerstone Letters to Speakers (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Post Cornerstone Freelen Party (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cornerstone - Student (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Cornerstone - Student Productions (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Cornerstone Invitation (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cornerstone Information Center (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cornerstone Accommodations - American Express (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Summary of Meal Signups, Cornerstone Weekend (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cornerstone Debriefing (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Cornerstone Implementation Task Force (Box 13, Folder 12-16)
  - George Shultz (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - London Centennial Conference 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Mexico City Centennial Conference 1990 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Toronto Centennial Conference 1990 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Hong Kong Centennial Conference 1990 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - International Centennial Celebration - Hong Kong (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - International Centennial Celebration - Mexico City (Box 14, Folder 3-6)
  - International Centennial Celebration - Toronto (Box 14, Folder 7-10)
  - Mexico City Conference Coverage, in Spanish (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mexico City Conference (Box 14, Folder 12-16)
  - Mexico City Conference Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Toronto Conference (Box 15, Folder 2-4)
  - Hong Kong Conference Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 5-7)
  - Hong Kong Conference News Coverage in English and Chinese (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Hong Kong Media (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
  - Hong Kong Conference Attendees Packet (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Davies Hall Concert, Dec 1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Davies Hall Tree (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - San Francisco Symphony Concert (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Mikhail Gorbachev (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Gorbachev Visit Planning (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Gorbachev Visit Press Kit (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gorbachev Visit, Stanford coverage (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Gorbachev Visit, National coverage (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - Original Message from Gorbachev (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Symposia List (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Information Explosion" Symposium (Box 16, Folder 14-16)
  - "Information Explosion" Symposium (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - "Ethnicity, Equity and the Environment" Symposium (Box 17, Folder 3-6)
  - "Beyond the Human Genome Project" Symposium (Box 17, Folder 7-11)
  - Symposium "New Vistas in Organic Chemistry, Jun 199 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Symposium "Novel and the Writer's Life, Feb 1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Pathology" Symposium in Hong Kong, Jul 1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Symposia Correspondence and Notes (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
  - Centennial Symposia Fundraising (Box 18, Folder 4-7)
  - Media Conference (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Media Conference 1987, Letters (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Media Conference 1987, Media Lists (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
  - Centennial Conference, Boris Pasternak, Oct 1990 (Box 18, Folder 12-13)
  - Centennial Conference, Orthopedic Grand Rounds, Feb 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Conference, Phonological Development, Sep 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Founders Day / Parents Weekend Working File (Box 19, Folder 3-5)
  - Centennial Founders Day and Finale Weekend (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Founders Day Program (Box 19, Folder 7-11)
  - Washington D.C. Centennial Event (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Photos from "Stanford Artists in New York" Exhibit (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Stanford South Florida Club Address, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Centennial Celebration San Diego 1989 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Centennial Celebration New York (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Centennial National Celebrations 1988-1990 (Box 20, Folder 2-4)
  - Centennial Celebration San Francisco 1988 (Box 20, Folder 5-7)
  - Bound Proposal, Stadium Spectacular from MSG (2 copies) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Bound Proposal, Stadium Spectacular from Jani (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Bound Proposal, Stadium Spectacular from USA Productions (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Bound Proposal, Registration from By Design (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Proposals for Centennial Videos (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
  - MPA Registration Management Proposal (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - CMS Registration Management Proposal (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - CMS Registration Management Contract (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - CMS Registration Booklet (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - CMS Correspondence, etc. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Proposals, Miscellaneous (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Television Public Service Announcements (Box 21, Folder 11-16)
  - San Francisco Examiner Sunday Image Magazine (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - Media Contacts (Box 22, Folder 3-6)
  - Centennial Video / Film (Box 22, Folder 7-8)
  - KRON-TV and Stanford Program (Box 22, Folder 9-12)
  - Pacific Bell Directory Cover (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Research Costs, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Media Articles on Stanford, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - USW Strike Threat (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Summary and Recommendations on Press Relations, 1988-1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Photographs from the Palo Alto Fete Parade, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Centennial Articles, Apr 1990 - Aug 1991 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
  - Centennial Articles, Sep - Oct 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - Articles on Stanford, Oct 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Magazine Articles, Sep - Oct 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Centennial Publications (Box 23, Folder 12-13)
  - Centennial Operating Committee
    - Centennial Operating Committee 1986 - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Centennial Operating Committee May 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Jul 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Oct 1989 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
    - Presentation to Centennial Reunion Leaders Jun 1990 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Apr 1990 (Box 24, Folder 8-9)
    - Centennial Operating Committee May 1990 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Jul 1990 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Sep 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1213)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Oct 1990 (Box 24, Folder 12-13)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Nov 1990 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Feb 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15-16)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Mar 1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Centennial Operating Committee May 1991 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Centennial Operating Committee Jun 1991 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Centennial Committee 1984 (Box 23, Folder 14-17)
  - Centennial Committee Meeting, Feb 7, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Meetings Folder (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Booklet: "The Stanford Centennial Campaign" (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Booklet: "Research and Scholarship at Stanford" (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Committee Lists (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Meeting Reports (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Annual Fund Celebrations Committee (Box 25, Folder 3-5)
  - Creative Planning Group (Box 25, Folder 6-9)
  - Centennial Staff (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Year Managers 1989 - 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - Centennial Memorabilia Committee (Box 25, Folder 14-16)
  - Centennial Creative Task Force (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee on Multicultural Planning (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
  - Ideas and Proposals (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
  - Centennial Media Advisory Group (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Communications Task Force (Box 26, Folder 9-14)
  - Centennial Correspondence 1979 - 1983 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Centennial Correspondence Jan - Jun 1985 (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
  - Centennial Correspondence Jul - Dec 1985 (Box 27, Folder 6-9)
  - Opening Convocation Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 10-11)
  - Discuss with George Shultz (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Discuss with Don Kennedy (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
  - Discuss with Pat Boesch (Box 28, Folder 1-3)
  - Discuss with Gerry Lieberman (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Discuss with Sue Cretarolo (Centennial Design) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Discuss with Dorothea / Georgiana (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Discuss with Maggie Kimball (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Discuss with Carolyn Manning (Box 28, Folder 8-9)
  - Discuss with Sandi Risser (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Discuss with Lois Wagner (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - Discuss with Susan Wolfe (Box 28, Folder 13-15)
  - Centennial Planning 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Finances 1986 - 1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Centennial 1986 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Red and White Celebrations 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Stanford History 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ideas (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Planning and Schedules (Box 29, Folder 3-4)
  - Centennial Year Proposals (Box 29, Folder 5-7)
  - Centennial Issues and Related Memos (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Postal Card Articles (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Art for Postal Card (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Centennial Postal Card (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Postal Card Celebration in Orange County (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
  - Postal Card - Hull House (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - USPS Board of Governors (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Postal Card Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - 1990 Redbook, US Postal Card Dedication Ceremony Sep 30, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - USPS Finale Cachet (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Commemorative Stamps (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Linn's U.S. Stamp Yearbook, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Leland Stanford Commemorative Stamp (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Opening Ceremonies Working File (Box 30, Folder 3-6)
  - Deukmejian, Feinstein, Wilson (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Hoover House Dinner (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Centennial Poster (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Olivera Centennial Poster (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Opening Ceremonies, VIP, Parking, Seating (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Opening Ceremonies, Invoices (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Opening Ceremonies, Littlefield Reception (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Opening Ceremonies, Frost Convocation (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Opening Ceremonies Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Opening Ceremonies Program (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
  - Opening Ceremonies (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
  - Opening Convocation Articles (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
  - Opening Convocation Memorabilia (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Red Book, Centennial Opening Convocation, Sep 30, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Louis Sullivan, US Secretary of Health and Human Services (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - October 1 Convocation (Box 31, Folder 8-9)
  - Convocation Luncheon, Oct 1, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Registration Memos (Box 31, Folder 11-12)
  - Registration Mailer (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Registration Packet memos (Box 31, Folder 14-15)
  - Stanford Alumni Association Registration Information (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Staff Registration and Volunteer Guidelines (Box 31, Folder 17-19)
  - Centennial Registration Material (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Booklet: Stanford Centennial Registration (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Registration Programs from Other Universities (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Staff Registration Program work materials (Box 32, Folder 2-3)
  - Registration Center (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Registration Work Materials (Box 32, Folder 5-9)
  - Registration Reports, Jun 1991 (Box 32, Folder 10-11)
  - Registration Reports, Jul 1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Registration Reports, Aug 1991 (Box 32, Folder 13-14)
  - Registration Reports, Sep 1991 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Staff Registration (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Cornerstone Registration Packet (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Finale Weekend Registration Packet (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Finale Weekend Interview Requests (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Finale Weekend Planning (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Finale Weekend Press Kit (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Finale Weekend Information Kit (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ted Koppel (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
  - Finale Weekend Roundtables (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - Finale Weekend Letters (Box 33, Folder 9-11)
  - Governor Pete Wilson and Senator Milton Marks (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Government Relations, Finale Weekend (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Salinas Convocation (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Salinas Finale Weekend Planning (Box 33, Folder 15-18)
  - Mulroney Convocation (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Mulroney Finale Weekend (Box 34, Folder 2-4)
  - Finale Weekend Keynote Enlistments (Box 34, Folder 5-8)
  - Don Kennedy, Finale Weekend (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Jerry Lieberman, Finale Weekend (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - George Shultz, Finale Weekend (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - The Finale Weekend Red Book (Box 34, Folder 12-15)
  - Booklet: Stanford Centennial Finale Weekend Program (2 copies) (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Centennial Finale Credentials (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Centennial Finale Weekend (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - Governor Wilson - Gay Rights Disturbance, Oct 1991 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Police Tape from Gay Rights Disturbance, Oct 1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Working Copy of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
  - First Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 8-9)
  - Second Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 10-11)
  - Third Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Fourth Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Fifth Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Sixth Draft of Finale Weekend Program (Box 35, Folder 15-16)
  - Finale Weekend - Saturday Welcome Back Receptions (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Palo Alto Weekly, "Finale Weekend" (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Commencement, Jun 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - 1991 Commencement Red Book (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
  - Centennial Commencement (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
  - Commencement Class Day (Box 36, Folder 6)